<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepages on EA Berlin</title>
    <link>https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepages on EA Berlin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/_career/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/_career/</guid>
      <description>Plan your high-impact career We recommend the 80,000 Hours career guide - free, evidence-based career advice tailored to talented graduates and young professionals. Feel free to contact us for informal feedback on your career plans.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/_contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/_contact/</guid>
      <description>Send us an email. We’re happy to answer questions, talk through career choices or discuss collaborations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/_first_section_text/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/_first_section_text/</guid>
      <description>What is Effective Altruism? Effective Altruism (EA) is a philosophy and social movement that uses evidence and reasoning to determine the most effective ways to help others. It&amp;rsquo;s a diverse community of researchers, entrepreneurs and philanthropists spread around the globe, working together on various causes such as AI safety, factory farming and global health to reduce suffering and improve lives effectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/_guiding_principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/_guiding_principles/</guid>
      <description> The Guiding Principles of Effective Altruism Commitment to Help Others Scientific Mindset Openness to Causes and Arguments Integrity and Honesty Collaborative Spirit </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/_learn_more/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/_learn_more/</guid>
      <description>Learn More Read up on the Effective Altruism key ideas and discuss them in the EA forum.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/_newsletter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/_newsletter/</guid>
      <description>Sign up to our email newsletter, follow us on Facebook and join our group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/_rationalists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/_rationalists/</guid>
      <description>Become your best self Check out Berlin’s Rationality Community - a group of people dedicated to self-improvement and truth-seeking with a large overlap to EA. They host regular rationality workshops, a dojo and a reading group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/_second_section_text/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/_second_section_text/</guid>
      <description>What does EA Berlin do? EA Berlin is one of of local EA groups around the globe, and serves as entry point to the community. We connect students and professionals interested in doing good effectively and support them in their personal development and career planning to increase their impact. We organize regular work meetups, discussion groups, workshops (career planning &amp;amp; rationality), career coaching, research projects, talks, networking events and socials.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/_sign_up_form/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/_sign_up_form/</guid>
      <description>Fill in our sign-up form to get invited to suitable events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/_third_section_text/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ea-berlin.org/homepage/_third_section_text/</guid>
      <description>Manche Projekte sind bis zu tausendfach effektiver als andere. Wir verwenden Logik und wissenschaftliches Vorgehen, um unsere Wirkung zu maximieren.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>